hikarabita kotoba wo tsunai de
connecting old words that have been used up
soredemo bokura shinpuru na omoi wo tsutaetai dake na no
I just want to convey my simple thoughts
fukinukeru kusunda ano hi no kaze wa
that day's faint wind blows away
kinou no haikyo ni uchi sutete
at the castle ruins of yesterday
kimi to warau ima wo ikiru no da
I'll laugh with you and live for the moment
soredemo ano dekigoto ga kimi wo kurushimeru daro
still that incident will continue to trouble you, right?
dakarakoso sayonara nanda
that's why it must be good-bye
konomama nanimo nokorazu ni anata to wakachiau dake
leaving nothing behind, let us share what is left
yagate bokura wa sore ga subetee dato kigatsuite
in time, we'll realize that it was everything
kanashimi wa hoo wo tsutatte namida no kawa ni naru dake
and sadness will touch our cheeks, creating a river of tears
yureru omoi wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte tokeau no yo
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex and melting away
Damn!
Pretty impressive...
You timed it well to scatter
the three to attack.
You must have practiced quite a bit, huh?
Since it is a pretty complicated song...
Well...
Not only did you
immediately understand
that I'm manipulating
these guys with my flute,
but you understood
how difficult this song is.
You're a pretty impressive punk.
But you can't completely
understand this song.
True... Since art is so foreign to me.
But since she uses that flute
to manipulate,
it means that song must contain
individually specific sound patterns
to control each and every movement
of those guys...
I'm pretty confident when it comes
to just analyzing
but this time it's not looking good.
The reason is...
I don't understand
musical notes whatsoever.
Fake!
Man Shikamaru
Gambles
to Recover From a
Hopeless Situation
I'll specially show you
the Camellia Dance next.
I'll crush you!
You shouldn't say things
you can't even do.
Shut up!
What?!
I told you.
This bone is harder than steel.
You should have a taste of it
with your own body.
Damn!
There's no one that's heard
this song and lived.
Finale Ninth Passage
Demon Revolution!
The melody's changed!
Something's gonna come!
What the...?!
What?
This is...?
The speed at which he flees
after determining
that these Material Ghosts
are dangerous...
Pretty impressive.
But...
I've used my precious Paper Bombs
and Smoke Bombs all at once
and all I could do was hide.
That white one...
bit off my physical energy.
Seeing that shuriken passed through
that thing is semi-materialistic
with very little mass.
It's Chakra itself with an appetite.
It's probably Chakra that's shaped
mostly by mental energy.
That's why it seeks stability
and craves for physical energy.
If I continue dealing with
those "Hungry Chakra"
I won't be able to build up my Chakra.
They're pretty dangerous.
She's a Shinobi who can
make special Chakra like me...
It's without a doubt a Secret Ninjutsu.
Which means I should leave
the white thing alone
and aim for the main body!
The quickest way would be
to stop the sound of the flute but...
it'd be impossible to get close to
that woman in this situation.
The next thing would be to capture
those three with Shadow Possession Jutsu.
But that's difficult too since they're
attacking me separately at different times.
If I let even one escape
I'd be attacked and it'd be the end...
There aren't any openings in
either offense or defense, this woman...
Heh! She might be
a pretty good Shogi player.
My remaining Ninja tools
are twelve kunai knives,
nine shuriken, twelve meters of wire,
one Flash Bomb, and one Paper Bomb...
Man...
I feel like I'm playing without
rooks or bishops.
Did I lose them?
I guess that's not possible...
Akamaru?
Here. Eat this, Akamaru.
If you don't eat you won't
get your strength back.
All right. Akamaru, let's go!
There's the issue of those guys too...
Dance of the Camellia!
There's no use hiding.
Unless you can predict
these guys' movements
there's nowhere you can run, little rat.
I'll find you and break you
into pieces right away!
Now then...
All right. Everything's ready.
All that remains is to do it.
There'll be nine attacks.
The outcome will be decided
during the attacks.
One!
Wishful thinking!
The Jutsu manipulated by
this sound is invincible.
Whatever plans you have
to win against me... is useless!
Two!
Scampering around you little rat!
Where are you?!
Three!
So you're over there!
Four!
So it's a cheap trick.
You think you can make a fool of me?!
Five... six...
seven... eight...
Scurrying around to get away.
What is he thinking?
Light?!
Nine!
Oh no!
He's lengthened the shadows
with light and...
Shadow Possession Jutsu!
Shadow Possession Jutsu...
a success!
That's impossible...
How were you able to predict
these guys' movements?!
There's no way you could have heard
the differences in my music patterns!
I wasn't listening to
the sounds at all.
There's something other
than the sounds
that give away your command patterns,
isn't there?
Your fingers!
It can't be!
The movement of the three...
Are you saying you memorized
my finger movements and predicted?
There's no way that's possible!
Your right index finger
and ring finger...
The sound that you make
with those
along with the left middle finger
and pinkie,
that middle crab pincher man
stands ready.
Your right thumb and index finger
and your left index finger and pinkie,
the club man charges.
While you were dodging my attacks
and looking for me,
I was observing each and every one
of your finger moves in detail...
analyzing and memorizing them.
It's no use...
They're bound by
Shadow Possession Jutsu.
The most interesting rule
of the Shogi play is that
you can use pieces you obtain
as your own pieces.
From here on out...
it's my turn to attack...
This time I'll hunt you down
using the three pieces.
You're looking pretty composed.
Stand ready with a kunai knife
at least.
My weapon is just this flute!
I told you that there hasn't been a person
who's heard the sound of
this flute and lived, idiot!
That's some confidence!
Retreat!
Too bad you aren't able to
use the pieces, hey!
Next, it's my turn!
What?!
Shadow Possession Jutsu
successful.
I told you.
That I'd hunt you down
using the pieces.
I used the three pieces as bait.
In attacking the first hand
is the trick a fake.
The basics are to score
with the second hand.
Bastard...
It can't be helped.
Now that it's come to this
I'll need to force out with power.
I didn't think that I'd get to
second state in a place like this...
It ticks me off but...
I'll acknowledge it.
This guy was pretty impressive trash.
What is... this?
It's true you're somewhat sharp but...
It won't go as
you've planned from here!
What?!
Is she gonna force herself out
of the Shadow Possession Jutsu?
What's with that tremendous Chakra?
The Jutsu's gonna come loose!
I can't be worrying about
saving Chakra anymore.
There's no other way
but to use that Jutsu!
Ninja Art: Shadow Strangle Jutsu!
Is he grabbing my body
with the shadow?
It's just as if I'm being grabbed
by a real hand...
But no more than this!
Damn! What incredible strength.
At this distance
I'll lose to that strength!
Take this!
Demon Flute: Chains of Fantasia!
This is bad!
Is this a... Genjutsu?
Where are you aiming?
I can't move my body...
While in second stage,
I manipulate many Genjutsu
with my flute.
Of those, this one is
an appropriate for that little rat.
The reason is...
This Genjutsu stops the movement
of the prey and ties it up!
How's that? How's it feel to
be the one tied up?
So this was your last move, huh?
Unfortunately, it's a return checkmate!
Little rat!
What...?
This guy...
He broke his own finger
with his own shadow!
Did he release the Genjutsu
with that pain?
On top of that he kept pretending to
be bound by the Jutsu?!
I told you this already
that the first hand is the trick
a fake.
The basics are to score
with the second move.
Moreover, this second move...
it's a little different from earlier.
With the Shadow Strangle Jutsu
the closer in distance you are
to the subject the stronger the hold.
Damn. I carelessly got too close...
No, that's not it.
The most careless thing was
the words you said earlier
"my weapon is just the flute."
You're looking pretty composed.
Stand ready with a kunai knife at least.
My weapon is just this flute!
I told you that
there hasn't been a person
who's heard the sound of this flute
and lived, idiot!
No way...
That's right.
The reason I threw the kunai knife
right in front of you and missed...
was to lead you to pick it up
and come closer to me, you see?
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
in my own words
boku nanka ga shaberi kaketara meiwaku ni omou ka na
would you think it was a bother if I approached you?
sonna fuan o kakaete yuuki o dashite mita yo
despite my doubts I worked up my courage
umaku shaberenai boku no fukiyou na hanashi
my clumsy attempts with words
kimi wa mimi o sorasazu ni chanto kiite kureta yo
you listened without turning away
sore dake de boku wa ukarete shimau no sa
no wonder I get carried away by you
dakedo kimi wa boku nante nantomo omottenai yo ne
but you don't feel anything for me do you?
setsunai yo
I feel so sad
dakedo
but...
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
in my own words
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
In my own words
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
No way, that's ridiculous!
Am I having a dream or something?!
But it's too intense to be a dream!
That suit with its outstanding
ventilation and supple fit.
On top of that, those eyes,
that hair, those eyebrows!
You! Why are you here...?!
Next time:
"Konoha's Green Beast Attacks!"
I sense the approach of a storm!